'use strict';

//questions and answers

const STORE = [
  {
    question: `Which creatures pull the carriages that take 
    students from the Hogwarts Express to the Castle?`,
    answers: ['thestrals','hippogrifs','goblin','acromantula'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: `Who was the headmaster of Hogwarts when the Chamber 
    of Secrets was opened for the first time?`,
    answers: ['Armando Dippet','Albus Dumbledore','Phineas Nigellus Black','Brutus Scrimgeour'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the room Harry uses 
    to teach Dumbledore's Army?`,
    answers: ['The Restricted Section of the Library',
      'The prefect’s bathroom',
      'The girls bathroom on the first floor',
      'The room of requirement'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: `Who is the Hufflepuff house ghost?`,
    answers: ['Cuthbert Binns',
      'Sir Patrtick Delaney-Podmore',
      'The fat friar',
      'The grey lady'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: `Slughorn teaches his students that Amortentia smells 
    different to each person. What food does Harry smell?`,
    answers: ['Pumpkin Juice',
      'Lemon drops',
      'Mrs Weasley’s fudge',
      'Treacle Tart'],
    correctAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: `What is the name of the book Hermione supposes Voldemort used to learn about Horcruxes?`,
    answers: ['Magik Moste Evil',
      'Secrets of the Darkest Art',
      'A Guide to Medieval Sorcery',
      'Moste Potente Potions'],
    correctAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: `Where is the Slytherin common room located?`,
    answers: ['Next to the kitchens',
      'In the West Tower',
      'The Dungeons',
      'Below the Great Hall'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: `In order they taught, who were the six Defence Against the Dark Arts professors who taught Harry at Hogwarts?`,
    answers: ['Quirrell, Lockhart, Lupin, Moody, Umbridge, Snape',
      'Quirrell, Lockhart, Lupin, Moody, Umbridge, Slughorn',
      'Quirrell, Lockhart, Lupin, Umbridge, Moody, Snape',
      'Quirrell, Lockhart, Lupin, Moody, Snape, Carrow'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  }, 
  {
    question: `How many staircases does Hogwarts have?`,
    answers: ['142',
      '143',
      '163',
      '152'],
    correctAnswer: 0,
  }, 
  {
    question: `Which Hogwarts professor was rumoured to be a duelling champion in their youth?`,
    answers: ['Minerva McGonagall',
      'Severus Snape',
      'Filius Flitwick',
      'Horace Slughorn'],
    correctAnswer: 2,
  }
];
